ILGWU Western States Region Records 5780/115
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Barajas-Silva, Agustin, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 21)
- Lopez-Lopez, Maria, 1979-1982 (Box 69, Folder 22)
- Hollander Confidential Files (Box 69, Folder 23)
- Quintero-Beltran, Isabel, 1973-1981 (Box 69, Folder 24)
- Albert's Bail Bonds, 1977-1981 (Box 69, Folder 25)
- Diaz-Ibarra, Ramon, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 26)
- Cabrera-Larios, Carlos, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 27)
- Vera-Verde, Amancio, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 28)
- Miranda-Ortega, Sofia, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 29)
- Salgado-Reyes, Jesus, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 30)
- Anguiano-Gonzalez, David, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 31)
- Barajas-Silva, Agustin: Immigration, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 32)
- Notices to Appear: Hollander, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 33)
- Russo Police Reports, 1975-1978 (Box 69, Folder 34)
- Gomez-Ortega Police Reports: Arias, Manuel, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 35)
- Ortega, Juan, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 36)
- Salazar Discovery Produced, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 37)
- Causo and Cooper Interviews, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 38)
- Renteria-Silva Police and City Attorney Reports, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 39)
- Machuca v. Romo Trinidad, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 40)
- Gomez, Fidel: Romo Trinidad, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 41)
- Silva, Danny: Police Reports, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 42)
- Zayas, Edgar: Information Produced Photo, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 43)
- Pendleton, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 44)
- Salazar, Marie: Police and City Attorney Reports, Not Arrested, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 45)
- Munoz-Arias, Park Pleating, Police and City Form, Trudy Slau, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 46)
- Reports: Police, 1978-1980 (Box 69, Folder 47)
- Pendleton: Police Reports, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 48)
- Salazar, Marie: Police and City Attorney Reports, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 49)
- People v. Govea: Davis Pleat Strike, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 50)
- Manny: immigration Application, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 51)
- Quinones, Rosemary: Criminal Case, Southern California Davis Pleat Strike, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 52)
- Valencia, Pedro: Criminal, 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 53)
- Ideal Pleating and Stitching Company v. ILGWU National Retirement Fund [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1983 (Box 69, Folder 54)
- Ideal Pleating and Stitching Company v. ILGWU National Retirement Fund [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1983 (Box 69, Folder 55)
- HRT Industries: Sick Pay Arbitration, 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 56)
- Morris Maler Shirt Manufacturing Company: Stevens Arbitration on Transfer, 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 57)
- San Francisco Joint Board, 1970-1972 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Seattle: Financial Reports, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Seattle: Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Union Health Center, 1965-1971 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Death Benefits, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- California Labor Federation: News Release, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles Joint Board: Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Transportation Vehicles, Incorporated, 1969-1971 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Central States Region: Frederick Siems, Personal, 1969-1972 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Impartial Chairman's Office, 1962-1972 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Supplementary Unemployment-Severance Benefits Fund: ILGWU, 1964-1967 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Requests: Donations and Contributions, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- California Farmer-Consumer Information Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- Injury Rates by Industry, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 14)
- Justice: Stein, Leon and Miller, Meyer, 1969-1973 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- KNXT Editorials, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Union Label News, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 17)
- A.I. Labor Letter, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- ALF-CIO Free Trade Union News, 1970-1972 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Israel Embassy: Miscellaneous Information, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 20)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 21)
- General Electric Strike, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- Film Requests, 1967-1971 (Box 70, Folder 23)
- California Rural Legal Assistance, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 24)
- Collective Bargaining, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 25)
- Congressional Record, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 26)
- California Labor Council on Political Education: News Release, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 27)
- Community Relations Conference of Southern California, 1970-1972 (Box 70, Folder 28)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 29)
- AFL-CIO Industrial Union Department: Miscellaneous, 1969-1973 (Box 70, Folder 30)
- California Council for Health Plan Alternatives, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 31)
- California Labor Federation: Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 70, Folder 32)
- Los Angeles Cloak Joint Board: Agreement, 1957-1970 (Box 70, Folder 33)
- Miscellaneous Locals: Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 70, Folder 34)
- Mexicali (Box 70, Folder 35)
- Occidental Life, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 36)
- Texas AFL-CIO: Lambert, G., 1970 (Box 70, Folder 37)
- Thank You Letters: Sent, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 38)
- University of California, Los Angeles: Industrial Relations, 1970-1973 (Box 70, Folder 39)
- Viewer Sponsored Television, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 40)
- San Francisco: Retirement, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 41)
- Provo, Utah, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 42)
- Financial Operations, 1969-1972 (Box 70, Folder 43)
- Fleischman of San Francisco, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 44)
- San Francisco Joint Board: Domenic Consoli, 1968-1971 (Box 70, Folder 45)
- ILGWU: By-Laws, 1947 (Box 70, Folder 46)
- Local 48: Italian Cloak Suit and Skirt Makers Union, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 47)
- Los Angeles County Federation of Labor: Arywitz, Sigmund, 1969-1972 (Box 70, Folder 48)
- Welfare Funds: Los Angeles Joint Board, 1957-1971 (Box 70, Folder 49)
- Joint Board Grievance and Appeal Cases: Minutes, 1966-1969 (Box 70, Folder 50)
- Wage Freeze Information, 1971-1972 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Finance Department: Reimbursement Statement, 1970-1971 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Portland, Oregon, 1963-1965 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Meeting Notes, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- San Francisco: Office Employees Agreement, 1968-1974 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- ILGWU National Retirement Fund, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- AMF Health Systems, Incorporated, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- ILGWU: Supplementary Unemployment-Severance Benefits Fund, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- ILGWU: Supplementary Unemployment-Severance Benefits Fund, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- ILGWU: Supplementary Unemployment-Severance Benefits Fund, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- ILGWU: Supplementary Unemployment Benefits Fund, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- ILGWU: National Retirement Fund, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- ILGWU: Supplementary Unemployment Benefits Fund, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 13)
- ILGWU: National Retirement Fund, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 14)
- ILGWU: National Retirement Fund, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Portland, Oregon, 1968-1972 (Box 71, Folder 16)
- Portland, Oregon: Associated Cloak and Suit Manufacturers, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- San Francisco: Welfare Fund, 1966-1972 (Box 71, Folder 18)
- ILGWU: Supplementary Unemployment Benefit Fund, 1965-1969 (Box 71, Folder 19)
- Joint Board Grievance and Appeal Cases: Minutes, 1966-1969 (Box 71, Folder 20)
- ILGWU: Incoming Members, 1975-1977 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- ILGWU: Incoming Members, 1975-1977 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- ILGWU: Incoming Members, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- ILGWU: Incoming Members, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Label Investigation Report, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Label Investigation Report, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- ILGWU: Incoming Members, 1975-1977 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Company Records, 1968-1975 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Label Sales, 1940-1974 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Label Deficiencies, 1965-1975 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Investigations: National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Investigations: National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Investigations: National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Unused Seminar Photos, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Union Label Show (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Armijo, Anita, 1975-1978 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- COPE: Memo, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Legislation: San Francisco, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Legal Decisions, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- The Declaration of Independence and The Constitution (Box 73, Folder 7)
- ILGWU, AFL-CIO: Leadership Training Manual, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous, 1975-1979 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Storz Instrument Company: Eye Instruments, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Portland, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Labor Documents, 1977-1981 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Technology, 1971-1978 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- ILGWU: Labor Organizations, 1975-1977 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Wolf, Max: S.I.C. Industrial Directory Information, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- Seattle, Washington, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 16)
- Whisper Soft Mills, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 17)
- Pacific Northwest District Council, 1975-1980 (Box 73, Folder 18)
- Simone, Tom, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 19)
- Committee on Political Education, 1979-1980 (Box 73, Folder 20)
- The Lubbers Nomination, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 21)
- ILGWU: Resolutions, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 22)
- Qualifications Appraisal Panels, 1972-1975 (Box 73, Folder 23)
- Tabak Tie-Ins (Box 73, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous: Law and Finance, 1978-1981 (Box 73, Folder 25)
- Targeted Coverage, Incorporated, 1982-1983 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Tatung Company of America, Incorporated, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Ted Stern Company, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- That's It, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Todd Rutkin, Incorporated, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Todd Rutkin, Incorporated, 1980-1981 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Torino Bakery, Incorporated, 1981-1983 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Torino Bakery, Incorporated, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Universal Pillow Company, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Uniworld General Incorporated, 1978-1979 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Val-Lanne Manufacturing Company, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- John H. Van Patten Company, Incorporated, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- John H. Van Patten Company, Incorporated, 1982-1983 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Wavecrest Company, 1977-1979 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Wells-Leigh of California, Incorporated, 1975-1976 (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Zipsort, Incorporated [folder 1 of 5], 1981-1982 (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Zipsort, Incorporated [folder 2 of 5], 1981-1982 (Box 74, Folder 17)
- Zipsort, Incorporated [folder 3 of 5], 1981-1982 (Box 74, Folder 18)
- Zipsort, Incorporated: Consolidated, 1982-1983 (Box 74, Folder 19)
- Zipsort, Incorporated [folder 4 of 5], 1981-1982 (Box 74, Folder 20)
- Zipsort, Incorporated [folder 5 of 5], 1981-1982 (Box 74, Folder 21)
- ILGWU: Finance Department (Box 77, Folder 1)
- ILGWU: Checks and Deposit Slips, 1978-1982 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Firm Law (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Credit Reports, 1959-1981 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous, 1962-1979 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Company Promotion, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Form 10-K, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Form 10-K, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Proxy Statement, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Prospectus, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Form S-7, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Form S-7, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- Form 10-Q, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- Form 10-Q, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- Prospectus, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Proxy Statement, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 16)
- Form 8-A, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 17)
- Form 10-Q, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 18)
- Form 10-Q, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 19)
- Prospectus, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 20)
- Proxy Statement, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 21)
- Form 10-Q, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 22)
- ILGWU, AFL-CIO: Authorization Card, 1976-1981 (Box 77, Folder 23)
- Textile Association of Los Angeles: West Coast Directory, 1974-1975 (Box 77, Folder 24)
- Staff Meetings, 1975-1979 (Box 77, Folder 25)
- Leaflets, 1968-1972 (Box 77, Folder 26)
- Letter Press (Box 77, Folder 27)
- Textile Association of Los Angeles: West Coast Directory, 1972-1973 (Box 77, Folder 28)
- Employment Development Department, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 29)
- National Apparel Suppliers and Contractors Directory: Western Edition, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- House Calls, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Labor Management Reports, 1979-1981 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Audit Reports, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Allard Electric, Incorporated, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Allied Auto Parks, Incorporated, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- AM International: Addressograph, 1980 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Appeals Committee Meeting, 1977-1979 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Arco Petroleum: Credit Cards, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Atlantic Savings, 1975-1979 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Air Conditioner Guide and Warranty: Westinghouse (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Harry Block, Impartial Chairman: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Blue Cross Claims, 1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Building Maintenance Catalogues, 1970 (Box 78, Folder 14)
- Byer, Sam: Collection Control Department [folder 1 of 2], 1980-1981 (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Byer, Sam: Collection Control Department [folder 2 of 2], 1980-1981 (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Buttner, AJ: File, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Index: Records System Classification, 1977-1980 (Box 78, Folder 18)
- Calculators/Typewriters/Duplicators, 1975-1979 (Box 78, Folder 19)
- California Division of Labor Statistics and Research File, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 20)
- California, Sacramento Franchise Tax Board for Bay Area Vacation Fund, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 21)
- California, Fresno Franchise Tax Board For Western States Region, 1979-1981 (Box 78, Folder 22)
- California, Sacramento Franchise Tax Board: ILGWU, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 23)
- California, Sacramento Franchise Tax Board for Southern California District Council, 1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 24)
- California Labor Federation, AFL-CIO, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 25)
- California Unemployment Insurance, 1979-1981 (Box 78, Folder 26)
- Census: By Local and Job Classification, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 27)
- Certificate of Flame Resistance: For Fire Department Inspection, 1975-1979 (Box 78, Folder 28)
- Charts of Accounts, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 29)
- Closed ILGWU Shops: Letters to Office of Labor Management Standards Enforcement, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 30)
- Day of the Sun: Jewish War Veterans of the United States, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 31)
- Death Benefit Fund, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 32)
- Department of Health, Education and Welfare for Los Angeles Vacation and Health Fund Correspondence, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 33)
- Equal Employment Opportunity Reports, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 34)
- 1st Quarter Federal and States Taxes: Los Angeles ILGWU Employers Vacation, Health and Welfare Fund, 1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 35)
- 4th Quarter Federal and States Taxes: Los Angeles ILGWU Employers Vacation, Health and Welfare Fund, 1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 36)
- General Correspondence For California Franchise Tax Board, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 37)
- Greenstone, Ellen: Correspondence File, 1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 38)
- Grievance Committee, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 39)
- Hawkins and Cooper: For Bay Area Welfare Fund and Vacation, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 40)
- Supplementary Unemployment Benefit Applications: Form DE 4846, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 41)
- Agreements, 1970-1976 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- S & E Button Company, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Segman, Bob, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Stevens Sportswear Company, 1974-1977 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Southern California-Davis Pleating Company, 1973-1974 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Edith Flagg, Incorporated, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Harris-Frank Clothing Stores, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Garment Haulers Association (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles Dress Company: Stanley Sunkin, Owner, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- Old Open Shop Investigations, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO County Federation Teamsters Communications, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- D.B. Reports, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- Robac Manufacturing Company, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Arnelle of California, 1974-1975 (Box 79, Folder 14)
- Associated Negotiations, 1972-1974 (Box 79, Folder 15)
- A.B.M. Corporation, 1973-1974 (Box 79, Folder 16)
- Negotiations: Bias Shops, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 17)
- Belt Association Negotiations, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 18)
- B&H Sportswear, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 19)
- California Bias, 1974-1977 (Box 79, Folder 20)
- Mari Bella, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 21)
- Contract Clauses, 1972-1974 (Box 79, Folder 22)
- D'Roma Coats: Covina, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 23)
- Standard Bias, 1971-1974 (Box 79, Folder 24)
- D'Anna Garment, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 25)
- Contessa of California, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 26)
- Deb, Susan, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 27)
- Domenico Manufacturers, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 28)
- Emblem Manufacturing Company: Negotiation File, Legal Papers, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 29)
- California Sportswear and Dress Associations, 1971-1977 (Box 79, Folder 30)
- Elena's Better Dresses, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 31)
- E Plus E, Incorporated, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 32)
- Sea Fashions, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 33)
- Fisher, Eva, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 34)
- Filro Negotiations: Clark and Tomigal, 1975 (Box 79, Folder 35)
- Frank Lee of California, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 36)
- Fisher Dress, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 37)
- Lou Gene of California, 1974-1975 (Box 79, Folder 38)
- Loubella Extendables, Incorporated: ILGWU, Negotiations, 1973-1977 (Box 79, Folder 39)
- Knits International, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 40)
- Designers Guild, Contracts, 1973-1974 (Box 79, Folder 41)
- G&G Sportswear, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 42)
- Star Glo Formals, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 43)
- Helga, Incorporated, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 44)
- Majestic Dress, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 45)
- Novis Denne of Arizona, Incorporated, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 46)
- Joe Karp Manufacturing Company, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 47)
- Jo-L Fashions, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 48)
- Margolis, Bernard, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 49)
- Lou Gene, Rio Fashions, 1972-1975 (Box 79, Folder 50)
- Kreiger, Louis, 1971-1974 (Box 79, Folder 51)
- California Sportswear and Dress Association, Incorporated, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 52)
- Messerman Sportswear, 1971-1974 (Box 79, Folder 53)
- Margolis, Bernard: Labor Consultant, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 54)
- Myers, Anna, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 55)
- Fredericks, Ivan, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 56)
- Jennifer, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 57)
- Frederick's Knits, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 58)
- Rothschild, Fred, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 59)
- Schnell Sportswear, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 60)
- Superior Bias Binding, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 61)
- Sabrina Coat, Incorporated, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 62)
- Star Button Company, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 63)
- Dove Manufacturing Company, 1959-1964 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Miss Elliette, 1961-1968 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- E.Z. Mills, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- E. T. Jrs., 1963-1966 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Elaine of Hollywood: Brassieres, 1963-1969 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Elaine Contracting, 1963-1964 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Elegant Miss of California (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Ellison of California (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Eres Couture, 1963-1969 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Renee Firestone, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Morris Fisher, 1969-1971 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Fresno Garment Company, 1963-1966 (Box 80, Folder 12)
- Frolic Time (Box 80, Folder 13)
- Isaac Fogelman, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 14)
- Edith Flagg, Incorporated, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 15)
- French Craft Leathergoods Company, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 16)
- Form-O-Uth [folder 1 of 2], 1959-1969 (Box 80, Folder 17)
- Form-O-Uth [folder 2 of 2], 1959-1969 (Box 80, Folder 18)
- Freis, Nathan, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 19)
- Fashion Time, Incorporated, 1963-1967 (Box 80, Folder 20)
- Fernbacher-Lobe, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 21)
- Fesco Associates, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 22)
- Harry Fink, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 23)
- Geno of California, 1965-1969 (Box 80, Folder 24)
- Gen-Way of California, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 25)
- Gerry of California (Box 80, Folder 26)
- Gill Shirt of California, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 27)
- Glydon's, Incorporated, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 28)
- Colden Girl, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 29)
- Gordon and Marx Sportswear, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 30)
- Graff California wear, 1961-1963 (Box 80, Folder 31)
- Grant Apparel Manufacturing Company, 1964-1967 (Box 80, Folder 32)
- Nick Grisanti (Box 80, Folder 33)
- Hank Gross (Box 80, Folder 34)
- Eddie George Sportswear, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 35)
- Haber Manufacturing Company, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 36)
- Holly Bra of California: Campaign, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 37)
- Holly Bra of California [folder 1 of 2], 1954-1968 (Box 80, Folder 38)
- Holly Bra of California [folder 2 of 2], 1954-1968 (Box 80, Folder 39)
- Hollybrooke of California, Incorporated, 1959-1966 (Box 80, Folder 40)
- Hollywood Blouse, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 41)
- Halo Lingerie, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 42)
- Hanco Cutting Service, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 43)
- Hart Coat Company, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 44)
- Helene's Buttons and Buckle Manufacturing Company, 1964-1967 (Box 80, Folder 45)
- Helene's Contracting (Box 80, Folder 46)
- Henry Fashions of California, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 47)
- HI-Fashions (Box 80, Folder 48)
- High Tide Swimwear, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 49)
- Hindy's Cutting Service, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 50)
- Irene, Incorporated: Campioni-Bert Geiger, 1964-1969 (Box 80, Folder 51)
- International Set, Incorporated, 1965-1969 (Box 80, Folder 52)
- Irma of California: Herbert Kruez, 1963-1969 (Box 80, Folder 53)
- Sig Isaac's (Box 80, Folder 54)
- Isabelle's Fashions, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 55)
- Issacs (Box 80, Folder 56)
- Item House, Incorporated, 1960-1964 (Box 80, Folder 57)
- Hollywood Needlecraft, Incorporated, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 58)
- Hollywood Ribbon Industries (Box 80, Folder 59)
- House of Gina, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 60)
- California Swimwear Company, Incorporated, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 61)
- Loubella Originals, 1958-1963 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Lou-Ette Originals, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Lou Gene of California, 1966-1967 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Lovable Company, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Lov'e Brassiere Company, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Lucille of Hollywood, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Lucinda, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Lykum of California, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Lynda Ann Sportswear (Box 81, Folder 9)
- La Mancha (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Lanz of California, 1967-1969 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- La Rose of California, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- Laven Manufacturing, 1968-1969 (Box 81, Folder 13)
- Miss Jilly, Incorporated, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 14)
- Marquel of California, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 15)
- Jack Marsee, Incorporated (Box 81, Folder 16)
- Martin of California (Box 81, Folder 17)
- Edith Martin Manufacturing Company, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 18)
- Marusia Originals (Box 81, Folder 19)
- Mary Ann Dress Company, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 20)
- Addie Masters, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 21)
- Maternity Shop, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 22)
- Barney Max, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 23)
- Maxwell Sheriff, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 24)
- Mermel of California, 1963-1965 (Box 81, Folder 25)
- Margorie Michaels, 1962 (Box 81, Folder 26)
- Alan Mickall, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 27)
- Milano: Norma Fashions, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 28)
- Jerry Miller, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 29)
- Murry Millman of California, Incorporated, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 30)
- Tommy Milo, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 31)
- Miss Pat, 1960-1968 (Box 81, Folder 32)
- Neal of California, Incorporated (Box 81, Folder 33)
- McFarlan, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 34)
- M.J.B., 1963 (Box 81, Folder 35)
- M&S Sportswear, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 36)
- Stuart Mackey, Incorporated (Box 81, Folder 37)
- Cliff Macklin of California, 1961-1962 (Box 81, Folder 38)
- Maeta, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 39)
- Maiden Form Bras, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 40)
- Marc Company, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 41)
- Marcela's of California, 1965-1967 (Box 81, Folder 42)
- Margie Shop, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 43)
- Marie of California (Box 81, Folder 44)
- Marie Elenes, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 45)
- Ronnie Marino, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 46)
- Marjorie Montgomery, 1963-1966 (Box 81, Folder 47)
- Willie Mark, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 48)
- California Swimwear Company, Incorporated, 1973-1974 (Box 81, Folder 49)
- Lizhan of California, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 50)
- Jeannette Hyland, Incorporated, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 51)
- Galanos Originals, 1961-1969 (Box 81, Folder 52)